<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Dr Anna Krystalli</title>
    <link>https://annakrystalli.github.io/categories/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Dr Anna Krystalli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the MIT license.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://annakrystalli.github.io/categories/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozsprint 2017 at the University of Sheffield</title>
      <link>https://annakrystalli.github.io/post/mozsprint-2017-at-the-university-of-sheffield/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://annakrystalli.github.io/post/mozsprint-2017-at-the-university-of-sheffield/</guid>
      <description>This post was first published on the Sheffield RSE blog

The 1st-2nd of June 2017 saw the Mozilla Global Sprint circle the globe for another time this year. It&amp;rsquo;s Mozilla&amp;rsquo;s flagship two-day community event, bringing together people from all over the world to celebrate the power of open collaboration by working on a huge diversity of community led projects, from developing open source software, building open tools to writing curriculum, planning events, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla StoryEngine Interview</title>
      <link>https://annakrystalli.github.io/post/2017-03-18-mozilla-storyengine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://annakrystalli.github.io/post/2017-03-18-mozilla-storyengine/</guid>
      <description>This interview was first published as part of the Mozilla StoryEngine Stories series and accompanied by a StoryEngine summary
Anna’s story Start by telling me a bit about your work. I’ve always loved working with data. As an undergraduate in Marine Biology and Oceanography, I worked with a large long-term survey data set looking into long term changes in fish egg abundance and timing. I continued work on it for my PhD in Macroecology, I where I also used some cool satellite derived environmental data to look at population dynamics at a regional scale and build models incorporating hydrographic structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenge of our generation: reproducible, transparent and reliable science</title>
      <link>https://annakrystalli.github.io/post/2016-09-02_isbe-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://annakrystalli.github.io/post/2016-09-02_isbe-2016/</guid>
      <description>Symposium summary: ISBE 2016, 3rd Aug, University of Exeter UK  This post was first published on the Mozilla Science Lab blog

When approached to help organise a post-conference symposium on reproducibility in science at the International Symposium on Behavioural Ecology, I jumped at the opportunity! The symposium was the brainchild of Malika Ihle and Isabel Winney, both post-docs here at the University of Sheffield at the time. As early career scientists, we share feelings of concern and disillusionment by the apparent reproducibility crisis engulfing our profession.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>